空に 浮かぶ 雲に乗って
I float in the sky, riding the clouds
終わる ことのない 旅へ行こう
I’m going in a journey with no end
揺れる 風になって
Becoming the swaying breeze
眠る月の夜は
On a night with a sleeping moon
煌めく 星になって
Becoming the twinkling stars
あなたを見つめてる
I watch over you
闇のとばり
Under a curtain of darkness,
静けさの中
In the midst of silence,
始まる
It will begin –
忘れかけた夢 追いかけて
A journey to chase the dreams
行く旅
That slipped away
ザビアツタ 時を越えて
Zabiatsuta – surpassing time
ザビアツタ 熱く燃えて
Zabiatsuta – burning bright
遥かかなた 地平線に
To the faraway horizon…
ザビアツタ 時を越えて
Zabiatsuta – surpassing time
ザビアツタ 熱く燃えて
Zabiatsuta – burning bright
今 燃え上がる
Flaring up now,
あの朝日のように
Like that morning sun…